{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419829043","data":{"timestamp":" 947419829042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bele"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419834421","data":{"timestamp":" 947419834420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bele"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419843710","data":{"timestamp":" 947419843710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bele"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419857292","data":{"timestamp":" 947419857292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__mri"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419863902","data":{"timestamp":" 947419863901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__mri"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419873826","data":{"timestamp":" 947419873826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__mri"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419887257","data":{"timestamp":" 947419887257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ebu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419894211","data":{"timestamp":" 947419894211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ebu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419903188","data":{"timestamp":" 947419903188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ebu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419935982","data":{"timestamp":" 947419935982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419943668","data":{"timestamp":" 947419943667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419954103","data":{"timestamp":" 947419954103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419964022","data":{"timestamp":" 947419964022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419982835","data":{"timestamp":" 947419982835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ofaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419990194","data":{"timestamp":" 947419990194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ofaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947419999643","data":{"timestamp":" 947419999643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ofaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420016225","data":{"timestamp":" 947420016225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420051762","data":{"timestamp":" 947420051762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420060188","data":{"timestamp":" 947420060188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420083124","data":{"timestamp":" 947420083124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__pira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420088935","data":{"timestamp":" 947420088935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__pira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420097242","data":{"timestamp":" 947420097242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__pira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420119521","data":{"timestamp":" 947420119521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__pira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420133178","data":{"timestamp":" 947420133178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__embe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420144491","data":{"timestamp":" 947420144491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eno"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420156570","data":{"timestamp":" 947420156570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eno"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420166239","data":{"timestamp":" 947420166239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eno"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420178299","data":{"timestamp":" 947420178299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eno"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420196522","data":{"timestamp":" 947420196522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420202622","data":{"timestamp":" 947420202622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420215827","data":{"timestamp":" 947420215826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" a63f0e2e-ecb3-440f-b89d-66d16cc98cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420257849","data":{"timestamp":" 947420257848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420263299","data":{"timestamp":" 947420263299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420271536","data":{"timestamp":" 947420271536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420287171","data":{"timestamp":" 947420287171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t_pe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420296670","data":{"timestamp":" 947420296670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t_pe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420314686","data":{"timestamp":" 947420314686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_ku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420327886","data":{"timestamp":" 947420327886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420337329","data":{"timestamp":" 947420337329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420345645","data":{"timestamp":" 947420345645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420356756","data":{"timestamp":" 947420356756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420373131","data":{"timestamp":" 947420373131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420382701","data":{"timestamp":" 947420382701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420391091","data":{"timestamp":" 947420391091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420408813","data":{"timestamp":" 947420408813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ale"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420419094","data":{"timestamp":" 947420419094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ale"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420426892","data":{"timestamp":" 947420426892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ale"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420439306","data":{"timestamp":" 947420439306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420450245","data":{"timestamp":" 947420450245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_aka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420456792","data":{"timestamp":" 947420456791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_aka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420465173","data":{"timestamp":" 947420465172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_aka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420474659","data":{"timestamp":" 947420474659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420481396","data":{"timestamp":" 947420481396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420489718","data":{"timestamp":" 947420489718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420497355","data":{"timestamp":" 947420497354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 503fd7c3-69d6-46f9-81e3-22103246398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_c_ako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420534693","data":{"timestamp":" 947420534693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_iwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420545902","data":{"timestamp":" 947420545902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420551591","data":{"timestamp":" 947420551590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420562388","data":{"timestamp":" 947420562388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420574602","data":{"timestamp":" 947420574602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ura"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420584952","data":{"timestamp":" 947420584951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ura"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420593682","data":{"timestamp":" 947420593682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ura"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420604920","data":{"timestamp":" 947420604919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_aka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420614457","data":{"timestamp":" 947420614457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_ji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420627595","data":{"timestamp":" 947420627595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420643857","data":{"timestamp":" 947420643857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420655424","data":{"timestamp":" 947420655423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420664177","data":{"timestamp":" 947420664177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420673175","data":{"timestamp":" 947420673174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_ku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420682653","data":{"timestamp":" 947420682652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420696284","data":{"timestamp":" 947420696282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 371c1345-47c5-42a2-9924-d6f4f62c12e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_c_ako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420752437","data":{"timestamp":" 947420752437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__keno"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420758630","data":{"timestamp":" 947420758629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__keno"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420767639","data":{"timestamp":" 947420767639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__keno"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420784787","data":{"timestamp":" 947420784787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__oma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420793589","data":{"timestamp":" 947420793589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__oma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420812156","data":{"timestamp":" 947420812155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__huru"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420828186","data":{"timestamp":" 947420828186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ete"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420895019","data":{"timestamp":" 947420895018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420901562","data":{"timestamp":" 947420901562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420910397","data":{"timestamp":" 947420910397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ote"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420916029","data":{"timestamp":" 947420916029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ote"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420923280","data":{"timestamp":" 947420923279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ote"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420938300","data":{"timestamp":" 947420938299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__hule"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420944062","data":{"timestamp":" 947420944062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__hule"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420958250","data":{"timestamp":" 947420958250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__hule"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420966434","data":{"timestamp":" 947420966432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__hule"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420982688","data":{"timestamp":" 947420982688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947420992317","data":{"timestamp":" 947420992316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421001656","data":{"timestamp":" 947421001655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421021771","data":{"timestamp":" 947421021771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ofaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421032145","data":{"timestamp":" 947421032144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421038417","data":{"timestamp":" 947421038416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421049576","data":{"timestamp":" 947421049575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421063078","data":{"timestamp":" 947421063077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421089495","data":{"timestamp":" 947421089494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_150949"," gameId":" 62953ec3-101f-4d68-9f7f-d377563862c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}